quavermusic.com 2017-04-15

# Privacy Policy

                                     Privacy Policy
QuaverMusic.com (“QuaverMusic.com”) is operated and presented to users in all locations by
Mastran Music Group, Inc., a Tennessee corporation d/b/a Quaver’s Marvelous World of Music.
This Privacy Policy describes the information practices of the QuaverMusic.com website (www.
QuaverMusic.com), including how we collect, use, and disclose personal information.
We are dedicated to safeguarding any personal information provided to or collected on the
QuaverMusic.com website. Accordingly, this privacy policy is provided to you in conformity
with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”), and the Family Educational
Rights and Privacy Act (“FERPA”). COPPA requires that we notify parents and legal guardians and
obtain consent from parents and legal guardians before we collect, use, and/or disclose personal
information collected from children under thirteen years of age. FERPA requires that we safeguard
and keep private student and teacher information that may be collected from an educational
institution for the sole purpose of providing services to that institution or an affiliated one.
1. What types of information do we collect?
     As described in this Privacy Policy, we directly collect from child users during our initial
     registration process a parent’s email address, the child’s account name, and the child’s
     password. The QuaverMusic.com website does not condition a child’s participation in
     an online activity on the child providing more personal information than is reasonably
     necessary for that activity.
     The QuaverMusic.com website requests, but does not require, child users to provide a
     parent’s valid e-mail address in order to register on the website. We use this information
     to send the parent a message that can be used to activate the QuaverMusic.com account,
     to notify the parent about our privacy practices, to send the parent communications
     either about the parent’s and child’s QuaverMusic.com accounts or about features of our
     website, and for the other purposes described in this Privacy Policy. This email address is
     correlated with the account user name.
     Educational Institutions have the option of providing an email address for registration
     in lieu of parent addresses, should they have a waiver from the parents on file. The
     Educational Institutions will also have the option of keeping student records, such as
     names, grades, and attendance, in our system and may provide that information to us
     through a software user interface or directly in a data file.
     We may also request a user name and e-mail address when a user submits a form through
     the “Contact Us” portion of the QuaverMusic.com website so that we may respond to the
     inquiry. We collect the e-mail address for the sole purpose of responding directly on a
     one-time basis to a specific inquiry.
     For some of our online activities - such as polls or surveys - we may ask users to provide
     information that is not personally identifiable, such as country of residence or a visitor’s
                                              Page 1 of 4                                     QP080115.2

   favorite music. We also enable users to chat online through our website, but we take
   measures so that users cannot communicate personal information through this chat
   function. These measures include intelligent and restrictive filters. Nevertheless, if you
   use the chat function within this website and disclose personally identifiable information,
   you should be aware that such information could be read, collected, or used by other
   users. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to
   submit through the chat function. Finally, we may offer blogs or other Public Forums
   as defined in the Terms of Use governing the website (the “Terms of Use”), as well as
   other features in which you may provide us with Submissions (as defined in the Terms
   of Use), but we take measures, including intelligent text filtering and restriction, so that
   users cannot communicate personal information through these Public Forums. If you
   use a Public Forum on this website, and disclose personally identifiable information, you
   should be aware that such information could be read, collected, or used by other users.
   We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit
   in these Public Forums.
   Additionally, when visitors come to our site, we may passively collect certain non-
   personally identifiable computer information, such as the type of computer operating
   system (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), the user’s IP Address, the web browser (e.g., Chrome,
   Internet Explorer) being used, the frequency with which guests visit various parts of our
   sites, and information regarding the Internet service provider, in order to continue to
   improve our sites and for various purposes related to our business. We may collect this
   non-personally identifiable information through the use of software technologies such
   as unique identifiers or “cookies.” Cookies are small text files that we place in visitors’
   computer browsers to store their preferences. You can choose to have your computer
   warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You
   do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your
   browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies
   off, you won’t have access to many features that make your Web experience smoother,
   and some of our services may not function properly.
   If you make a purchase online we collect financial information necessary to process the
   order. We do not use this financial information for any purpose other than processing
   payments to QuaverMusic.com. The financial information that you enter to purchase a
   membership is not stored by QuaverMusic.com; instead it is retained by our payments
   processing vendor for the purpose of processing credit card payments made to
   QuaverMusic.com. If personal information is not provided to us, then QuaverMusic.com
   may not agree to QuaverMusic.com membership and may not be able to provide access
   to certain content and functionality on the QuaverMusic.com website, or to provide
   other information, products, or services which may be requested.
2. How do we use your personal information?
   In addition to the purposes described in Section 1, we may actively collect and use e-mail
   addresses and user names to track usage and to ensure users are following the site’s
   Terms of Use. In addition, we may use an e-mail address and user name to ban a user
   temporarily or permanently from the QuaverMusic.com website if that user engages in
   inappropriate conduct on the site. We may also use e-mail addresses and user names to
   enable parents to review Personal Information that the children have submitted to the
   QuaverMusic.com website and to provide notification regarding the site, such as any
   future amendments to this Privacy Policy. We also may use information in the aggregate
   to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services. In all cases, we
   comply with FERPA guidelines and do not share student records with any third party.
                                             Page 2 of 4                                    QP080115.2

    We may disclose information where we are required to do so by law, for example, in
    response to a court order or a subpoena or where we disclose information (but not
    FERPA-protected information) to service providers or other group companies who
    provide support for the operations of our website and who do not use or disclose the
    information for any other purpose. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we also
    may disclose Personal Information in response to a law enforcement agency’s or other
    public agency’s (including schools or children services) request or if we feel that such
    disclosure may prevent the instigation of a crime, facilitate an investigation related to
    public safety, or protect the safety of a child using our website, protect the security or
    integrity of our website, or enable us to take precautions against liability.
    If we sell all or part of our business or make a sale or transfer of our assets or are otherwise
    involved in a merger or business transfer, we may transfer Personal Information to a third
    party as part of that transaction, to the extent permitted by applicable law. Finally, we
    may transfer Personal Information and store it outside of the area in which a member of
    QuaverMusic.com is located.
3. Do we ever disclose your personal information that we collect from
   children to third parties?
    We do not allow third-party companies to solicit or advertise to our users. Our intention
    is to keep QuaverMusic.com free from any of this sort of direct advertising. We do not
    share student data protected by FERPA, except as stipulated in that Act for the purposes
    of carrying fulfilling our contractual obligations to provide services to educational
    institutions.
4. How do we secure Personal Information?
    The security of your personal information is important to us. We have put in place
    appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help
    prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information
    we collect online.
5. How may you contact us to ask additional questions?
    Please contact our Privacy Director as provided below if you would like to access the
    Personal Information that we have collected online from you or your child, correct
    factual errors in such information, request to have this information deleted, or request
    that we no longer collect or maintain such information. Please be sure to include your
    e-mail address and a telephone number where we can reach you. To protect you and
    your child’s privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity
    before granting you access to the personal information that we collect and maintain
    about you or your child.
    If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please send
    an e-mail with your questions or comments to privacydirector@QuaverMusic.com or
    write us:
                                              QuaverMusic.com
                                        c/o Mastran Music Group, Inc.
                                            Attn: Privacy Director
                                             1706 Grand Avenue
                                         Nashville, Tennessee 37212
    Please be assured that any personal information that you provide in communications
    to the above e-mail and postal mail addresses will not be used to send you promotional
    materials, unless you so request.
                                                Page 3 of 4                                      QP080115.2

We reserve the right to change the privacy policy at our sole discretion. QuaverMusic.
com users will be informed of any such change by us posting a new privacy policy on the
QuaverMusic.com website and the effective date of any change of privacy policy will be
clearly marked. As required by law, we will not use Personal Information in ways that are
materially different from the ones described in this Privacy Policy without also providing
notification of such practices and obtaining consent to any such different uses. If we
make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by e-mail, or by means of a
notice on our home page.
                                        Page 4 of 4                                    QP080115.2
